Register of the Walter Henry Judd papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- AUDIOVISUAL FILE, 1942-1976
  - Photographs, circa 1961-1966
    - 5 prints (1 duplicate) of Dr. Judd with others inspecting troops in Europe, 1951; 2 prints of Dr. Judd and Congressional group with Mohammad Ayub Khan and other officials in Pakistan, 1957; 1 print of conference group at U.S.-British Parliamentarians meeting Bermuda, 1962 (Envelope W)
    - 5 prints (1 duplicate) of Dr. Judd with others inspecting troops in Europe, 1951; 2 prints of Dr. Judd speaking at a World Federalists meeting, 1950; 6 prints of a post-election luncheon for Dr. Judd's staff?, 1954; 1 print of Wolf Ladejinsky and others at a locomotive plant, 1959 (Envelope X)
    - 1 print of Dr. Judd receiving an honorary degree. circa 1950; 3 prints of Dr. Judd with Anna Chennault and others, 1974; 4 prints of Dr. Judd with unidentified individuals, undated; 4 prints of Dr. Judd with fellow members at FMC gatherings, 1979 and 1981 (Envelope Y)
  - Motion picture film, circa 1961-1966 (Film shelf)
    Ten reels primarily relating to foreign affairs and communism.
- SCRAPBOOKS, 1942-1962 (Boxes 274-297)
  Primarily clippings; also includes copies of speeches and writings. Arranged by form, thereunder by date.
  - General
    Primarily campaign material and clippings relating to Dr. Judd.
    - 1942 (Box 274)
    - 1942-1944 (Box 275)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 276)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 277)
    - 1946 (Box 278)
    - 1947 (Box 279)
    - 1948 (Box 280)
    - 1949 (Box 281)
    - 1950 (Box 282)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 283)
    - 1952 (Box 284)
    - 1953 (Box 285)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 286)
    - 1954 (Box 287)
    - 1955 (Box 288)
    - 1955-1957 (Box 289)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 290)
    - 1958-1960 (Box 291)
    - 1960 (Box 292)
    - 1961 (Box 293)
    - 1962 (Box 294)
    - 1962 (Box 295)
  - Speeches and writings
    - 1943 (Box 295)
    - 1959 (Box 296)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 297)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 297)